

CONTACT:

kalamarcin1@gmail.com 505 866 447 Tri-City

LinkedIn: Link Repository: Link

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- React
- Git
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Affinity Designer
- Adoby InDesign

LANGUAGES

English - B2 Polish - native

GENERAL SKILLS

- · Creative problem solving
- Team work managing and coordinating a team of 15 most experienced employees from all departments
- · Decision making and responsibility coordinating and supervising recruitment processes in all departments
- · Continuously striving to improve
- · Flexibility and innovation

INTERESTS

- · Digital illustration
- Drawing
- · Watercolor and acrylic painting
- · Fantasy and science fiction literature

MARCIN KALA

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

For many years I worked as a graphic designer creating visual identification and DPT. From an early age I created simple websites in HTML and CSS. I graduated coding bootcamp of the Software Development Academy - Frontend Developer. I am a person focused on personal development and learning new skills. I feel good both in a team and working independently.

SELECTED IT PROJECTS:

PORTFOLIO

HTML, SCSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT

Github: Link | Preview: Link

GITHUB USER SEARCH APP

HTML, SCSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, API

Github: Link | Preview: Link

ORDER FORM WITH VALIDATION

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT

Github: Link | Preview: Link

EDUCATION:

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT ACADEMY

Frontend Developer 03.2022 - 11.2022 (285 h)

HTML and CSS / Git / Basic programming / CSS preprocessors / CSS and RWD frameworks / TypeScript / Developer tools (NodeJS, npm, Webpack) / Principles of good design / Structural programming in JavaScript / Object-oriented programming in JavaScript / React / CMS / Scrum / Software testing

POMERANIAN HIGHER HUMANITIES SCHOOL IN GDYNIA

English philology 2010 - 2012 (interrupt)

WORK EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Freelance | 2010 - present

- visual identification
- DPT

TRAINING & OPERATIONS MANAGER

Hard Rock Cafe Gdańsk (Lyon, Hamburg, Kraków) | 2017 - 2021

- · Conducting training for new and permanent employees
- Providing constant coaching and guidance to department trainers to ensure consistency and quality of training